<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="leg_plot">
        <item name="story1">You leave your town unsure of what the world has in store for you, but excited at the prospect of this new adventure.</item>
        <item name="story2">You come upon a Pump-kin village, half burned to the ground. The villagers say that the monsters abducted a third of the town to be baked into pies. You help them build fortifications before moving on.</item>
        <item>You sight an Elf stronghold in the distance and decide to stay there for the night. As you approach the gate they command you to leave. The stronghold appears to be on lockdown to ward against monster attacks, and you don’t feel like tussling with the club-waving guards, so you pitch your tent in the nearby woods.</item>
        <item>You come across a band of fellow adventurers and ask them what they know of the monster attacks. One of them, a Birdperson, says they heard that the Math’head were responsible, the disdain for the race’s interest in manipulating natural law evident in his chirpy voice. A Math’head of the party takes offense but admits that such may be the case, although she wouldn’t know either way, and suggests you visit a nearby Math’head city. </item>
        <item>The Math’head city bustles with activity as the people are mobilized to combat the monster hordes. Units of Mathemagicians bustle along the walls, casting wards. You visit the College of Mathemagic, but are asked to leave after you insinuate that the fundamental theorem of calculus could be used to mutate the naturally occurring wildlife. It appears this lead was a dead end, and you continue onward.</item>
        <item>Though you know not where your adventure is leading you, the increasing strength of monsters and the increasingly visible destruction suggests that you grow ever nearer to to the monsters’ origin. Luckily for you, you aren’t the novice that you once were.</item>
        <item>You spend the night with an Elf hunting party who offered to share some of their fresh venison. Though a rough and warlike people, their martial skills seem to have helped them bear the brunt of the current calamity better than others.</item>
        <item>You find another Pump-kin village, in distress due to the destruction of their irrigation channels. The mayor, an old man over a year old, explains the town’s worry that the next harvest may not be productive enough to fully populate the town. The monster attacks must be stopped to end this suffering.</item>
        <item>As you ask around yet another city, you’re approached by a Birdwoman and led to what appears to be a camp of refugees at the edge of town. The Birdwoman says that although this group chose to flee, many more have stayed in their towns in the Birdpeople homeland, awaiting the rapturous end times prophesied by an upstart religious sect. They say, says the Birdwoman, that the hordes are The First Sign. Though skeptical, you decide to head east, into the mountains, to investigate this new lead.</item>
        <item>The Birdpeople do seem disproportionately affected by the monster hordes. Each day you pass more parties of refugees fleeing the Birdperson homeland in the eastern mountains. Are you finally approaching the answers you seek?</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>