<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="leg_plot">
        <item name="story1">You leave your town unsure of what the world has in store for you, but excited at the prospect of this new adventure.</item>
        <item name="story2">You come upon a Pump-kin village, half burned to the ground. The villagers say that the monsters abducted a third of the town to be baked into pies. You help them build fortifications before moving on.</item>
        <item>You sight an Elf stronghold in the distance and decide to stay there for the night. As you approach the gate they command you to leave. The stronghold appears to be on lockdown to ward against monster attacks, and you don’t feel like tussling with the club-waving guards, so you pitch your tent in the nearby woods.</item>
        <item>You come across a band of fellow adventurers and ask them what they know of the monster attacks. One of them, a Birdperson, says they heard that the Math’head were responsible, the disdain for the race’s interest in manipulating natural law evident in his chirpy voice. A Math’head of the party takes offense but admits that such may be the case, although she wouldn’t know either way, and suggests you visit a nearby Math’head city. </item>
        <item>The Math’head city bustles with activity as the people are mobilized to combat the monster hordes. Units of Mathemagicians bustle along the walls, casting wards. You visit the College of Mathemagic, but are asked to leave after you insinuate that the fundamental theorem of calculus could be used to mutate the naturally occurring wildlife. It appears this lead was a dead end, and you continue onward.</item>
        <item>Though you know not where your adventure is leading you, the increasing strength of monsters and the increasingly visible destruction suggests that you grow ever nearer to to the monsters’ origin. Luckily for you, you aren’t the novice that you once were.</item>
        <item>You spend the night with an Elf hunting party who offered to share some of their fresh venison. Though a rough and warlike people, their martial skills seem to have helped them bear the brunt of the current calamity better than others.</item>
        <item>You find another Pump-kin village, in distress due to the destruction of their irrigation channels. The mayor, an old man over a year old, explains the town’s worry that the next harvest may not be productive enough to fully populate the town. The monster attacks must be stopped to end this suffering.</item>
        <item>As you ask around yet another city, you’re approached by a Birdwoman and led to what appears to be a camp of refugees at the edge of town. The Birdwoman says that although this group chose to flee, many more have stayed in their towns in the Birdpeople homeland, awaiting the rapturous end times prophesied by an upstart religious sect. They say, says the Birdwoman, that the hordes are The First Sign. Though skeptical, you decide to head east, into the mountains, to investigate this new lead.</item>
        <item>The Birdpeople do seem disproportionately affected by the monster hordes. Each day you pass more parties of refugees fleeing the Birdperson homeland in the eastern mountains. Are you finally approaching the answers you seek?</item>
        <item>You enter a Birdperson village, smoldering ruins surrounding the barricade protecting the few remaining homes. And yet many still live here. True to the Birdwoman’s testimony, a street preacher preaches fire and brimstone to an ashen congregation. “The Eagle God has come again!” he shouts, “as the ancient scrolls have foretold, its armies shall wipe the world clean and reshape it in our feathered image!” As the crowd chirps praises to their god, you decide you must discover any truth in the preacher’s words.</item>
        <item>Every village you come across is rapt with religious fervor. The remaining Birdpeople seem wholly consumed by the Eagle God movement; any dissenters must have evacuated or been slain. Your questions are met with antagonism. The monsters get ever stronger.</item>
        <item>Finally, an old Birdman opens up to you. He says that the “cultists” arrived suspiciously soon before the monster onslaught. Birdpeople folklore has tales of the Eagle God, yes, but it was assumed they were childrens’ stories. The Birdman explains that unlike the fabled Eagle God, a spirit of benevolence, the Eagle God of the cultists is one on the warpath, sending out its monstrous hordes to wipe the slate clean and establish a new world of Birdperson dominance. You thank the old Birdman and he points you in the direction the cultists came from.</item>
        <item>You’re attacked by Eagle God cultists in the woods. After defeating them in combat, you find a strange talisman in one of their pockets. What appears to be a map is engraved on the side - maybe this is their headquarters?</item>
        <item>After following the map you arrive at a cliff face. Confused, you reach out your arm, which passes right through. Moving through the wall you find yourself in a well lit cavern - this must be the cultist base. You sneak around, avoiding cultists as you go, and find yourself in some kind of storage room. You manage to steal letter after letter of archived cultist correspondence and make your way out. </item>
        <item>The cultists’ letters explain their original goals. A group of Birdperson conjurers had been attempting to summon forth the Eagle God when their spell went awry, turning the divine might of the Eagle God against them. It appeared to open a rift in the sky through which the monsters have been pouring into your dimension. The conjurers seem to have pivoted towards appeasing the Eagle God to save their own skins, as well as exploit their own people in the process.</item>
        <item>Another letter questions the Eagle Gods’ divinity. The cultist higher-ups seem unsure whether the powerful entity they summoned is in fact a deity or simply a particularly powerful monster from another plane - this would apparently explain its ability to tear a hole to its own dimension. If this is the case, you should be able to defeat the Eagle God in combat like any other monster, thereby sealing the portal. You just need to find it.</item>
        <item>You manage to subdue one of the leaders of the Eagle God cult. He says he had been there when they summoned the God forth, on the top of the tallest mountain in the northern range, where the boundary between realities is at its thinnest.</item>
        <item>You round a hill and suddenly see the mountain in the distance, it dwarfs those around it, capped by stormclouds. Above it: an apparition, the rend in reality itself, formless but distinctly unnatural. Even at this distance it fills you with a sense of dread, but you know you must keep pushing forward.</item>
        <item>You eat dinner with a hermit who lives in a cave at the base of the mountain. When you tell him of your quest he gives you his blessing. You feel you’re going to need it.</item>
        <item>You crest the mountain top and behold your quarry: the Eagle God sits before you, its massive winged frame perched upon a crag. The portal to the Eagle’s dimension hangs above you in the sky, a warping that your mind cannot seem to focus on. Suddenly, with a cry, the god notices you, and your battle begins. </item>
        <item>You strike the final blow, and with it sever the Eagle God’s grasp on the mortal plane. The tear in the sky seems to knit itself back together as the god dissolves into dust and is blown away by the mountain wind. The people shall sing of your victory for generations, but for now your job is not yet done: the monsters the Eagle unleashed still roam the earth...</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>